(Penny:)Yeah.
(Leonard:)Funny how things work out.
But he loved the companionship
and the wisdom...
(Toby:)...that his own father failed to provide.
(Sheldon:)Your parents made the right decision.
(Toby:)I cannot work like this.
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
ON TV]
(Toby:)This is amazing, just sitting on a couch
watching TV with a woman.
(Toby:)Not being drunk or high
or wondering if you're a dude down there.
(Penny:)Leo, you are a very sweet,
really funny guy.
(Penny:)You're gonna do okay.
(Toby:)One day at a time, Penny.
(Toby:)One day at a time.
How long is he going to stay here?
(Sheldon:)He's a homeless drug addict, Leonard,
where is he going to go?
(Sheldon:)Boy, you have a lot to learn about lying.